Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Local 807 (Auburn, NY) Additional Records 5869
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Local 807 (Auburn, NY) Additional Records
1911-1988
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen (BLF&E)
BLF&E Local 807
5869
5.89 cubic feet
5.9 linear ft.
Records (documents).
This collection consists of the records of Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Local 807, located in Auburn, New York. They were collected by William J. McLane, local chairman, and also include the records of the successor unions for this group of employees.
5722553
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Elizabeth Parker, March 06, 2014
EAD encoding:
Elizabeth Parker, December 04, 2017
Biographical / Historical
The Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen was founded on December 1, 1873 in Port Jervis, New York by Erie Railroad firemen in order to provide mutual support for railroad firemen. Their first convention was in 1874, at which they adopted their first constitution. The Brotherhood initially emphasized insurance, but by the late nineteenth century had branched out into labor-management relations.
In 1907, the organization changed its name to the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen [BLF&E], reflecting the changes in its membership as former firemen were promoted to engineers and permitting locomotive engineers to join its ranks. In 1969, the union merged with the Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen, the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, and the Switchmen's Union of North America to form the United Transportation Union [UTU].
Lodge 807 of the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, now defunct, was located in Auburn, New York. It was composed of employees of the Lehigh Valley Railroad Company [LVRR] working on the Lehigh Valley, Auburn, Cortland, and Auburn-Ithaca branches. These employees were represented by Lodge 807 until its dissolution in 1966 at which point they were represented by Lodge 379, located in Sayre, Pennsylvania. After the merger of the railroad brotherhoods, they were represented by UTU Local 810. Finally, in the 1970s, the operating employees joined the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers [BLE], Division 380.
Scope and Contents
Inclusive date range: 1911-1988
Bulk dates: 1959-1979
This collection consists of the files of William J. McLane, Local Chairman of BLFE Lodge 807 (Auburn, NY), Local Chairman of UTU Local 810 (Sayre, PA), and finally Local Chairman of BLE Division 380 (Sayre, PA) for the Auburn and Cortland, New York area employees of the Lehigh Valley Railroad. It primarily documents the history of Lodge 807, but its files also document the transitions its members went through during the downsizing and consolidation of both the carriers and of the operating brotherhoods. The records in this collection amply document the effects union consolidations and mergers had on the general membership.
The collection contains historical records from the founding of Lodge 807, including documentation of the founding of a new Lodge, the transfer of existing BLFE members from other Lodges into the newly formed Auburn, New York Lodge, the applications of Lehigh Valley Railroad Company [LVRR] Auburn Division to join Lodge 807, and correspondence with the Grand Lodge for guidance. Membership lists are attached to these pieces of correspondence. Of particular interest is a Ritual Book from 1945, offering instruction to members on how all ceremonies were to be performed in the Lodge.
This collection contains extensive records on the daily operations of a BLFE Lodge from the first half of the 20th century. Financial filings from 1958-1967 and the financial secretary's cashbook from 1937-1967 offer an in depth view of the Lodge's activities as well as complete membership rosters, and in the cases of insurance plans, the member's family and next of kin. These records, along with the seniority rosters for the railroad facilities, make this a rich resource for genealogists.
This collection also contains numerous case files resulting from grievances file by employees. The case files are instructive in that there are both those cases settled at the local level as well as cases that had to be forwarded to the sitting general chairman of the Grievance Committee to be further addressed. The correspondence that resulted from these cases extensively documents the relations between members at various levels in the BLFE's hierarchy.
This collection also documents the effect the crew consist dispute and the final decision of Arbitration Board No. 282 had on firemen and engineers.
Finally, this collection contains documentation of the effects the bankruptcies and consolidations of the carriers had on their employees and the unions that represented them.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5141: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Records 5141 G: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Graphics 5141 MB: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Memorabilia 5176: Grand Lodge of the Ladies Society of the Former Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Records 5467: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Local 807 (Auburn, NY) Records 5475: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen General Chairman, Boston and Maine Railroad Records 5611: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Honorary Register of Disabled 5646: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Additional Records 5467: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Local 807 (Auburn, NY) Records 6176: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Additional Records
Railroads--Employees.; Railroads -- Employees -- New York (State) -- Auburn; Grievance procedures. Railroads. New York (State); Locomotive engineers; Locomotive firemen; Railroads -- Mergers; Labor unions -- Mergers -- United States; Labor unions -- Consolidations -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Grievance procedures -- United States; McLane, William J.; Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen.; Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen. Local 807 (Auburn, N.Y.); Railway Labor Executives Association; Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employes; Lehigh Valley Railroad Company; Penn Central Transportation Company; ConRail; Amtrak
5722553
- Constitutions, 1963-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  BLFE: 1963, 1976 Grand Lodge, BRA: 1971, 1975 UTU Unification: 1968, 1971
  - Item 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1976; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Constitution and Bylaws of the International Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers
    Format: Pamphlet.
  - Item 2: Constitution of the Grand Lodge, 1974; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Constitution of the Grand Lodge- Statutes for the Government Lodges and Protective Laws (circa 1974)
  - Item 3: Constitution of the Grand Lodge, 1975; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Constitution of the Grand Lodge- Statutes for the Government Lodges and Protective Laws
  - Item 4: Constitution of the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1963; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Constitution of the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen
  - Item 5: Unification Agreement and Constitution, 1968; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 1)
    United Transportation Union= Unification Agreement and Constitution
  - Item 6: Supplement to Constitution, 1971; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 1)
    United Transportation Union- Supplement to Constitution
- "Ritual" Book, 1945; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 2)
  February 1, 1945
- Agreements with Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1939-1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Agreement, 1939; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Leigh Valley Railroad Co.- Agreement Between the Lehigh Valley Railroad Co. and Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees
  - Item 2: Agreement, 1944; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Leigh Valley Railroad Co.- Agreement Between the Lehigh Valley Railroad Co. and Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes
  - Item 3: Agreement, 1948; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Leigh Valley Railroad Co.- Agreement Between the Lehigh Valley Railroad Co. and The Order of Railroad Telegraphers
  - Item 4: Agreement, 1956; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Leigh Valley Railroad Co.- Agreement Between the Lehigh Valley Railroad Co. and Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers
- Agreements with New York Central Railroad, 1958; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Agreement, 1958; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 4)
    New York Central Railroad- Agreement Between the New York Central Railroad Co. and the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers
  - Item 2: Agreement, 1958; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 4)
    New York Central Railroad- Agreement Between the New York Central Railroad Co. and the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen
- Agreement with ConRail, 1979; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Timetables for Lehigh Valley and ConRail, 1968-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Lehigh Valley Timetable No. 9: 1968 ConRail, Northeastern Region, Timetable No. 3: 1984
  - Item 1: Time Table No. 3, 1984; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Lehigh Valley Railroad- Time Table No. 3
  - Item 2: Time Table No. 9, 1968; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Lehigh Valley Railroad- Time Table No. 9
- Rule Books and Safety Instructions, 1954-1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  First Aid Instructions, 1963; LVRR Safety Rules, 1959; LVRR Rules Book, 1954
  - Item 1: First Aid Instructions, 1933; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Association of American Railroads- First Aid Instructions for Employees
  - Item 2: Safety Rules, 1959; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Lehigh Valley Railroad Co.- Safety Rules, governing Employees of the Transportation Dept.
  - Item 3: Schedules of Pay, 1954; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Lehigh Valley Railroad Co.- Schedules of Pay, Rules and Regulations for the Government of Firemen (helpers), Hostler and Hostler Helpers
- Lehigh Valley Railroad Rulings, booklets, 1950-1958 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Rulings, 1955; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Lehigh Valley Railroad Co.- Rulings, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen
  - Item 2: Rulings, 1956; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Rulings, 1957; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Lehigh Valley Railroad Co.- Rulings (Book No. 4), Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen
  - Item 4: Rulings, 1958; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Lehigh Valley Railroad Co.- Rulings (Book No. 5), Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen
  - Item 5: Rulings, 1950; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Time Books (for recording earnings), 1967-1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  two blank booklets
  - Item 1: Time Book, 1967; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Enginemen's Time Book, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen
  - Item 2: Time Book, 1979; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 9)
    1979 Time Book, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen
- Benefits and Insurance Pamphlets, 1962-1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Unemployment Sickness Survivors Retirement, 1962; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Railroad Employes- Unemployment Sickness Survivors Retirement
  - Item 2: National Group Insurance Plan, 1972; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Railway Labor Organizations- National Group Insurance Plan
  - Item 3: Railroad Retirement and Survivors Benefits, 1979; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Railroad Retirement and Survivors Benefits, for railroad workers and their families
- Railway Digest of Development and Comments, 1959; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Volume 14, Number 3. March, 1959
- Lehigh Valley Grievance Procedure manual, 1967; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Investigations, instructional pamphlets, 1956-1963 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: You Are Hereby Notified, 1956; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 13)
    You Are Hereby Notified to present yourself for investigation
  - Item 2: Investigations, 1959; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Investigations at Interpretative Index of First Division Awards with Supplementary Material
  - Item 3: Investigations, 1873; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Investigations- Fair and Impartial, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen
  - Item 4: Award 20401, 1955; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Award 20401, The purpose is to caution against the inadvertent waiver of the right to proper notice by the manner in which the question is answered with respect to having received notice to attend the investigation. (circa 1955)
- BLE Pocket Protector, Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 14)
- United Transportation Union Welcome packet, 1972; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Mediation Agreement, 1972; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Mediation Agreement, Case A-8381 between Railroads Represented by the National Carriers' Conference Committee and their Employees Represented by the United Transportation Union
  - Item 2: Mediation Agreement, Case A-9152, 1972; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Mediation Agreement, Case A-9152 between Railroads Represented by the National Carriers' Conference Committee and their Employees Represented by the United Transportation Union
  - Item 3: B.E. Pamphlet 20-G, 1967; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 15)
    B.E. Pamphlet 20-G, for Trainmasters and Train and Engine Crews
  - Item 4: B.E. Pamphlet 20-F, 1967; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 15)
    B.E. Pamphlet 20-F, for Yardmasters, Yard Crews and Yard Clerks
  - Item 5: Welcome to the Craft of Locomotive Firemen, 1973; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 15)
    United Transportation Union- Welcome to the Craft of Locomotive Firemen
- Local Chairman Booklets, 1955-1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: What are the Attitudes and Attributes of a Successful Local Chairman?, 1955; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 16)
    What are the Attitudes and Attributes of a Successful Local Chairman?, Symposium of July 9, 1955, Chicago Switching District
  - Item 2: A Discussion of the Hours of Service Act, 1962; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 16)
    The Hours of Service Act, a discussion
  - Item 3: Principles of Interpretation of Agreements, 1962; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Construction of Contracts: Principles of Interpretation of Agreements, with Illustrative Excerpts from the National Railroad Adjustment Board First Division
  - Item 4: What Makes Them Tick?, 1962; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 16)
    What Makes Them Tick?: A Look at the Men who Man the Trains
  - Item 5: Hours of Service Act as Amended by Public Law 91-169, 1973; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Hours of Service Act as Amended by Public Law 91-169, effective December 26, 1970
- Preliminary Views on Rail Restructuring, 1975; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Comments of the Rail Services Planning Office. January 10, 1975.
- Reports, 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  General Chairmen's Duty Reports, 1963-1966 Secretary-Treasurer's Quarterly Reports, 1963-1966 Audit, 1963-1966
- Membership to Lodge 807, 1927-1966 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Labor Organizations Annual Financial Report; form LM-3, B-57, 1965; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 20a)
- Labor Organizations Annual Financial Report; form LM-3, B-57, 1964; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 20b)
- Labor Organizations Annual Financial Report; form LM-3, B-57, 1963; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 20c)
- Labor Organizations Annual Financial Report; form LM-3, B-57, 1962; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 21a)
- Labor Organizations Annual Financial Report; form LM-3, B-57, 1959; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 21b)
- Labor Organizations Annual Financial Report; form LM-3, B-57, 1960; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Labor Organizations Annual Financial Report; form LM-3, B-57, 1961; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Labor Organizations Annual Financial Report; form LM-3, B-57, 1964; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Labor Organizations Annual Financial Report; form LM-3, B-57, 1967; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 25)
  (not a complete filing)
- BLFE Local 807, Old Files, 1911-1936 (Box 1, Folder 26a)
- BLFE Local 807, Old Files, 1958-1969 (Box 1, Folder 26b)
- National Mediation Board, Arbitration Board No. 282: Award Documents, 1963; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 27)
  Crew consist dispute
- National Mediation Board, Arbitration Board No. 282: Award Documents, 1964; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 28)
- National Mediation Board, Arbitration Board No. 282: Award Documents, 1965; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 29)
- National Mediation Board, Arbitration Board No. 282: Interpretations, 1966; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Award of Arbitration Board 282 and Interpretations Rendered by the Reconvened Arbitration Board, 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Award of Arbitration Board 282. Reference Book., 1963; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Financial Secretary files, 1959-1969 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Hours-of-Service Act, 1960-1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Mileage Reports, Cortland, New York, 1959-1964 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- General Grievance Committee. Quarterly Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1969 (Box 2, Folder 1a)
- General Grievance Committee. Quarterly Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1969 (Box 2, Folder 1b)
- General Grievance Committee Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Case File re Leaving Engine at Other than Designated Point. Article 18, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Case File re Meal Allowance. Case F-64-118, 1965; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Case File re Difference in Earnings, 1965; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Case File re Trip to East Ithaca, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Case Fil re Holiday Pay. Case F-65-03, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Case File re Final Terminal Delay Payment, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Case File re Deadheading, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Mileage Reports. Cortland, New York, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 10a)
- Mileage Reports. Auburn, New York, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 10b)
- Case File re Other Class of Services. Article 7, 1965-1969 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Case File re Two Starts Out of Terminal, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Case File re Lap Back. Article 78., 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Case File re Switching at Geneva. Case F-66-42, 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Case File re Switching at Terminal. Articles 56-65. Case F-66-43, 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- General Grievance Committee. Quarterly Reports, 1959-1962 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Cases Sent to General Chairman Sullivan, 1958; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Denied claims sent to William H. Sullivan, General Chairman, for further handling.
- Mileage Reports. Auburn, New York, 1948-1960 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Mileage Reports. Cortland, New York, 1949-1955 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Letters from Riley, General Chairman, BLFE, 1960-1964 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Vacations, 1962; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Crew Violations, 1966; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Case File re Held for Service. Article 47. Case F-64-26, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Firemen's Extra List. Cortland, New York and Sayre, Pennsylvania, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Case File re Advance Boarding Time. Case F-66-23, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Vacation, 1957-1960 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Case File re Switching at Ithaca yard. Case F-67-15, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Case File re Switching at Auburn Yard. Case F-66-40, 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Case File r Switching at Cortland Yard. Case F-65-12, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Mimeographs from G.C. Riley, General Chairman, BLFE, 1961; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 30)
  Correspondence and copies of bulletins, pamphlets and announcements from general Chairman's office.
- Cases Sent to Buffalo and Riley, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  For further handling.
- Mimeographs from Riley and Grand Lodge [folder 1 of 2], 1962; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 32a)
  General pullet ins and correspondence.
- Mimeographs from Riley and Grand Lodge [folder 2 of 2], 1962; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 32b)
  General bulletins and correspondence.
- Correspondence from Riley re General Grievance Committee Cases, 1962; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Special Board of Adjustment No. 466, 1963; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Engineers' Agreements, 1951-1962 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Claims Handled with Chief of Personnel. Auburn, New York and Cortland, New York [folder 1 of 2], 1957-1965 (Box 2, Folder 36a)
- Claims Handled with Chief of Personnel. Auburn, New York and Cortland, New York [folder 2 of 2], 1957-1965 (Box 2, Folder 36b)
- Agreements, System: Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1942-1963 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Mimeographs from Dressler and Grand Lodge, 1964; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 38)
  Bulletins and general correspondence
- Correspondence, General Grievance Committee, 1963; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, General, 1949-1959 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Cases Sent to Dressler and Crowley, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 3a)
  J. E. Crowley, Superintendent, LVRR E.A. Dressler, General Chairman, BLFE
- By-Laws of the General Grievance Committee, 1960; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 3b)
  Revised December22, 1960
- Mimeographs From Grand Lodge and General Chairman, 1963; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Includes bulletins, newsletters, and general correspondence
- General Grievance Committee: Audits and Quarterly Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 5a)
- By-Laws of the General Grievance Committee, 1963; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 5b)
  Revised January 10, 1963
- General Grievance Committee: By-Laws, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1959-1961 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- BRAC: magazine, newsletter, and Cayuga NY documents, 1957-1981 (Box 3, Folder 7a)
  Railway Clerk Interchange, November 1977- October1978; BRAC Newsletter, November 18, 1981
- BRAC: collective bargaining agreements, 1966-1979 (Box 3, Folder 7b)
- Special Board of Adjustment No. 460: BLFE vs. LVRR. Award No.s 10-15, 1963; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Mimeographs and Letters from General Chairman Riley, 1957-1960 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Cases Written to Buffalo and Riley, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Case File re Seniority Status of Auburn-Cortland Fireman, 1962-1965 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Correspondence re General Grievance Committee cases, 1960; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 12)
- B-57 Forms, 1958; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 13)
- B-57 Forms, 1963; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 14)
- B-57 Forms, 1965; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Contains correspondence re deaths of members and benefits paid to their families
- B-57 Forms, 1966; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 16)
- LM-3 Report, 1966; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 17)
- LM-3 Report, 1967; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Contains terminal report to IRS, stating the organization, Lodge 807, had been dissolved on September30, 1967. Its members were transferred to Lodge 379 in Sayre, Pennsylvania.
- LM-3 Report, 1960; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 19)
- LM-3 Report, 1962; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 20)
  From letter requesting additional LM-3 Report forms from the Grand Lodge
- Lehigh Valley Railroad Veterans' Association newsletters, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- ConRail Magazine, vol. 3, issue 3, 1978; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 22)
  October 1978
- ICC Safety and Service Board orders, 1962; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Investigation into Ithaca Derailment, 1981; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Proposed Revision of Industrial Code Rule No. 42, 1960; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 25)
  Relating to sanitation and shelter for railroad, Pullman, and Express Company employees
- Concerted Movement of 1963 Report, 1964; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Health and Welfare Agreement, 1964; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Correspondence with UTU general Chairman, C.A. Cunningham, 1969; Pamphlet (Box 3, Folder 28)